EF字幕组
猎人
第一季 第3集
猎人 前情提要
Previously on Hunters...
那则音频信息中说会发生流血事件 现在的确发生了
That audio message said blood would be spilt, and it has been.
那个带走艾比的混球
The bastard who took Abby.
只要我们找到他 就能找到你妻子
We find out where he is, we find your wife.
我老婆怎么会是你们中的一员呢
My wife is not one of you.
现在想看艾比吗 来吧
You wanna see Abby now? Come on.
我们在仓库里的尸体上采集了一些证物
We got some forensics off the body in the warehouse.
发现受害者体内有海洛因
Turns out there was heroin in the victim's system.
不是艾比
It's not Abby.
我们无处不在 我们所向披靡
We're everywhere, and you can't stop us.
是斯拉维奇的妻子
Slavich's wife.
我把那女人撕成碎片
I tore that woman to shreds,
就像野兽一样 我还喜欢那种感觉
like an animal... and I liked it.
里根特工就像眼镜蛇一样蜕皮
Agent Regan is shedding like a freakin' cobra.
斯拉维奇跟我说的最后一句话就是我们组里有内鬼
Slavich's last words to me were about Hunters being inside the ETU.
里根很困惑
Regan's confused.
他觉得她是他们中的一员
He think she's one of them.
她最好小心
She better watch herself.
塞克莱顿市 西弗吉尼亚州 1997
- 嘿  - 怎么了 艾莉森
- Hey! - What is it, Allison?
你能不能别玩这个
Could you play something else?
你在逗我吗
Are you serious?
噪音刺得我头疼
The noise hurts my head.
你这人真奇怪
You are so weird.
艾莉森
Allison?
发生什么了
What happened?
你做了什么
What'd you do?
这是意外 爸爸
It was an accident, Daddy.
- 哦 我的天哪  - 对 对不起
- Oh, my God. - I'm... I'm sorry!
- 她没事的  - 泰德 发生什么事了吗
- She's okay. - Ted, everything all right out there?
我们需要帮助 快报警
We need help! Call 911!
打电话报警  他们需要帮助
Call 911! They need some help!
猎人
我们在麦卡锡仓库内找到的瘾君子尸体内
The junkie body we found in McCarthy's warehouse
有哥伦比亚·奥尔维多的海洛因
had Columbian Olvidos' heroin in her system.
翻译 ICE  ZH
美国缉毒局去年拍到麦卡锡和五胞胎还有奥尔维多在一起的照片
DEA got pictures of McCarthy and the Quins with the Olvidos last year.
翻译 oo  Ginny
校对/后期 Ginny
他们对自己面临的事情完全不了解
They had no idea who or what they were dealing with.
五胞胎  是我在仓库见到的那些怪胎
Quins? Those are the freaks I saw at the farmhouse.
对 这是我们起的名字
That's what we're calling 'em.
发生了什么
What's happening?
这些照片是在通往
This picture was taken on a road
压制  猎魔人
哥伦比亚丛林深处一制毒窝点的路上拍的
leading to a drug compound deep in the Columbian jungle.
猎人和海洛因 还有如穆斯林圣战者般的藏身地点
Hunters and heroin, and deep like a Mujahidin situation.
统筹  Ginny
那是筹集资金的最佳方法
Tried and true method of raising funds.
女童子军有饼干 恐怖分子有毒品
Girl Scouts have cookies, terrorists have dope.
里根 你听明白了吗
Regan. You getting all this?
猎人在丛林里倒手毒品
The Hunters are running drugs in the jungle,
你让我和一个新来的人去找他们
and you're sending me a new guy to find them.
- 收到  - 算上我
- Got it. - Count me in.
卡罗尔特工有啃药史 布里格斯
Agent Carroll has history with narcotics, Briggs.
我不是担心他
It's not him I'm worried about.
你难道认为我需要保护吗
You think I need protecting?
不如问问杰西·斯拉维奇吧
Oh, let's ask Jessie Slavich.
因为有里根特工在 你才能坐在这里 闭上你的嘴
Agent Regan is the only reason you're still here to shoot your mouth off.
你和卡罗尔
You and Carroll.
我个人认为
My two cents...
如果我们要去丛林抓猎人的话 多一个士兵不是坏事
if we're going into the jungle to catch Hunters, another soldier couldn't hurt.
好吧 布里格斯 算你一个
All right... Briggs, you're in.
共同合作 找到他们的大本营 捣毁它
Work together, find this camp, shut it down.
抓住任何你能找到的猎人或是同伙
Capture any Hunters or collaborators you may find.
我们之前用过几个当地人
There are some local guys we've used before.
你们可以相信他们
You can trust them.
我来处理麦卡锡的善后工作
I'll handle the McCarthy cleanup.
就这样
That is all.
我要拿走这些
I'm taking these.
你的全家福吗
Family pictures?
开玩笑啦
I was kidding.
别那么严肃
Lighten up.
你依然是位已婚男士吧
Thought you were still a married man?
我不会在这里处理我的皮肤问题的
I'm not getting down to my skin in here, so...
嗯
Yeah.
关于你的皮肤
About your skin thing.
还要讨论这个
We're still on that?
请便
Go on.
还有没有其他方法
Is there any other way to, you know,
辨别某人是不是……
tell if someone is... whatever you are.
我有强烈的欲望 生理上的
I get urges, physical urges.
很难控制
They're hard to control.
你说生理是指
You mean physical like...
是的 没错  还有
Yes, that. And other stuff.
冲动
Impulse control.
饥饿 愤怒
Hunger, rage.
她在抱怨自己的感觉吗
Is she blaming her feelings?
接着就得开始抱怨经前综合征了吧
Next she'll say it was PMS.
饶了她吧
Give her a break.
江山易改本性难移
A tiger doesn't change its stripes.
我们要去的地方 将需要她发挥身上的每一个长处
Where we're going, were gonna need everything she's got in her.
塞克莱顿市 西弗吉尼亚 1997
艾莉森 你在做什么
Allison... what are you doing?
你说过那个声音会刺痛你的耳朵
You said that hurts your ears.
确实是这样
It does.
亲爱的
Sweetie...
你对妮可做的 不过是个意外
What happened to Nicole... was a mistake.
不 不是的
No, it wasn't.
我想让她停下 所以就推了她
I wanted her to stop, so I pushed her.
但你并不想伤害她
But you didn't mean to hurt her.
这不是你的错
This was not your fault.
可是贾妮和安布尔说是我的错
Janine and Amber said it was.
她们说不想再跟我做朋友了
They told me they're not gonna be my friends anymore.
你之所以会对妮可做那样的事是因为
The reason this happened to Nicole...
我们和一般人不太一样
is because we're different.
你 我 你的妈妈
You... me, your mom.
我要告诉你真相
I'm gonna show you the truth.
可能会有点吓人
And it might be scary.
希望你能足够强大勇敢
But I need you to be strong.
现在 仔细看好了
Now, watch closely.
尽量不要转过身
Try not to turn away.
爸爸 不要  停下 快停下
Daddy, no! Stop! Stop!
- 看着 看好了  - 爸爸 不要这样
- Keep... keep watching. - Dad, please!
不要转头 艾莉森
Don't look away, Allison.
这就是我们的本来面目
This is what we are.
它在我身体里 也在你身体里
This is in me, and it's in you, too.
这也是你伤害妮可的原因
And it's why you hurt Nicole...
我身体里没有这些  没有
That isn't inside me. It isn't.
嘿 没事的
Hey... it's okay.
没事的
It's okay.
我从来没想过要伤害别人
I don't ever want to hurt anyone.
那就不要有这个念头
Then don't.
博亚卡  哥伦比亚
只靠我们自己 永远都找不到任何东西
We'll never find anything in here on our own.
他们会出现的 他们可是职业杀手
They'll turn up. They're hired guns.
不出现 就不会有钱
No show, no dough.
嗨
Hi.
早上好
Good morning.
我叫卡罗尔
I'm Carroll.
这是布里格斯  里根
This is Briggs. Regan.
杰克逊派我们来的
Jackson sent us.
你们中谁是头儿
One of you the C.O.?
亚历杭德罗
Alejandro.
但他们
But they...
叫我马托
call me Mato.
欢迎来到我的丛林
Welcome to my jungle.
奥尔维多的毒品营地就在这片丛林的某处
The Olvidos' drug camp is somewhere in this part of the jungle.
如果一定要我说的话 我估计在这
I had to guess, I'd say here.
但你也不确定吧
But you don't know for sure?
那片种植园可是由冷血杀手经营的
The plantation is run by cold-blooded killers.
一定藏得严严实实
They keep it hidden.
营地周围都布满陷阱和狙击手
Guard the perimeter with traps and snipers.
而我们这里的人都是 纯爷们
And these guys... puro cabrons.
前多国部队指挥官
Former MFC.
军人
Military.
还有哥伦比亚革命武装力量
That and FARC.
他们都是些
They're soldiers we grew up with
宁愿拿报酬干活也不要逍遥自在的家伙
who decided they wanted a payday instead of freedom.
你应该感谢杰克逊和他在中情局的朋友
You can thank Jackson and his CIA friends for that.
所以守卫糖果店的都是些小孩子
So they got kids guarding the candy store.
糖果店的主人是小孩子
Kids own the candy store.
而奥尔维多家族 他们从不开玩笑
The Olvidos, they don't play.
要是你偷东西的话 他们会把你眼睛挖出来
They cut your eyes out for stealing.
但如果是你的话
But you...
他们可能会索取点别的
但从没有人能闯入那个营地
But no one has ever made it to that camp uninvited.
军队 缉毒局 都不曾有过
Not the army, not your DEA... no one.
你们确定要这么做吗
You're sure you want to do this?
怎么 你害怕了
Why, you getting cold feet?
我
Me?
没有 我只想确定 大难临头之时
No... I just want to be sure you won't run away
你会不会转身就逃
when the fan hits the shit.
你还是担心自己吧
You worry about your own.
我们绝不会当缩头乌龟
We're sure as hell not backing down.
马托说制毒营地就在十英里开外的地方
Mato says the drug camp is ten miles in.
他傍晚前会把我们带到那里
He'll get us there by nightfall.
对于一个在坎大哈（阿富汗城市）执行过任务的人来说 这都不算什么吧
Not bad for a guy who did his tours of duty in Kandahar.
我宁可去阿富汗 也不愿意来这种满是蕨类植物的山沟
I'd take Afghanistan over this FernGully shit any day.
我也讨厌绿乎乎的东西
Yeah, I hate this green stuff, too.
你不是吃素么  这些在你眼里 不就跟沙拉一样么
You're a vegetarian. Isn't this all just... salad?
我现在是跟着朵拉(卡通片人物）去探险么
Now I'm being led by Dora the Explorer.
态度放尊重点
Best keep that attitude to yourself.
我们必须谨慎
We need it.
尤其猎人就在附近之时
Especially if there are Hunters out there.
奥尔维多的欢迎方式
An Olvidos welcome.
女士优先
Ladies first.
你听见什么动静了吗
You hearing anything?
放下武器  等一下  放下武器
Drop the weapon now! Hold on! Drop!
马托
Mato!
- 不要开火  - 等等
- Hold fire! - Wait!
不要开火
Hold fire!
是工人
Workers.
有武器
Armed.
足以杀掉我们所有人
They could have killed us all.
放下武器
Drop the weapon.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
别害怕 你现在已经安全了
Don't worry, now you're safe.
我不会伤害你的
I'm not gonna hurt you.
你现在没事了
You're okay now.
你安全了
You're safe.
他们是你的家人吗
This is your family?
对吗
This?
你的家人呢
What happened with your family?
她从林子里冲出来 带走了我妈妈
She came out of the jungle and took my Mom.
她说了什么
What did she say?
有人从林子里冲出来 带走了她妈妈
Someone came out of the jungle and took her mother.
小妹妹
Friend.
是谁
Who?
谁带走了你妈妈
Who took your Mom?
怪物
A monster.
塞克莱顿市 西佛吉尼亚州 2005年
艾莉森
Allison!
艾莉森 开门
Allison, open the door!
你在干嘛  你疯了吗
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
- 不就是大麻么  - 你现在必须离开这儿
- It's just weed. - You need to leave, now.
啊 天啊
Oh, my God!
刚刚那是地震吗  出什么事了
Was that an earthquake? What's happening?
我跟你说过的那些人 那些不可信的人
The people I told you about, the ones we can't trust.
他们在这里  来吧 快点
They're here. Come on, hurry.
我的耳朵
My ears!
妈妈
Mom!
爸爸 我好害怕
Dad, I'm scared.
出什么事了
What's happening?
拿着这个  爬上阿勒格尼山
Take this. Climb Allegheny.
跟着你的直觉走
Follow your instincts.
我脱身后会去找你的
I'll come get you when I can.
但我不能就这么走了  妈妈怎么办
But I can't just leave. What about Mom?
艾莉森 听着 你要勇敢
Allison, listen, I need you to be my brave girl.
好吗  跟直觉走就好了
Okay? Just follow your instincts.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
赶紧从窗户出去  现在  马上
Now out the window. Now. Go, now!
她说一只怪物带走了她的母亲
She says a monster took her mother.
怪物  什么样的
A monster? How it was?
什么样的
How it was?
再问问她
Ask her again.
我们需要弄清楚她到底看到了什么
We need to know exactly what she saw.
是拉莫哈娜
It's La Mojana.
当地传说里的人物
It's a local legend.
一个可以改变外形的女人
A woman that changes shape,
引诱人进丛林 然后吃了他们
takes people into the jungle and eats them.
毒枭宣传这个传说以阻止农民进入丛林
The cartel encourages it to keep peasants out of the jungle.
是莫哈娜吗
It was the Mojana?
带走你妈妈的那个人
That took your Mom?
是的  拉莫哈娜
Yes. La Mojana.
拉莫哈娜
La Mojana.
我们得把她带回她的营地
We need to get her back to the camp.
不不不  她就待在这里
No, no, no... she stays.
前方险阻未知
We're walking into a shit storm,
我需要人手 抓一个是一个
and I need every soldier I got.
她还是个孩子
She's just a kid.
我要把她带回去
I'm taking her back.
你有任务
You got a job to do...
和我们一起
with us.
弗林说得没错
Flynn's right.
哦  出现了个拉莫哈娜
Oh... we got La Mojana out there,
你就突然离不开我咯
and suddenly you need me.
唷 芭比大兵 她是个大姑娘啦
Yo, G.I. Joe Barbie, she's a big girl.
我在她那么大的时候 都手撕好几人了
I was slitting throats when I was her age.
你想拿到之前杰克逊答应的薪水吗
You want your payday like Jackson promised?
让你最弱的手下带这姑娘回营地
Send your weakest man to take the girl back to camp,
不然的话 我们来带
otherwise, we take her.
你就什么也捞不着
And you go home empty-handed.
你做决定吧 头儿
Choice is yours, jefe.
卡洛斯
Carlos.
卡洛斯 把这女孩儿带回营地
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气
You're welcome.
走吧
Let's go.
什么时候告诉他 我们是在打怪物 而不是对抗毒枭
When do we tell him we're fighting monsters and not a drug cartel?
什么也不用说
We don't tell them anything.
而且他们也不是怪物
And they're not monsters.
他们只是非人类罢了
They're just not human.
阿勒格尼山脉 西弗吉尼亚州 2005
如果你在读这个的话 说明我已经不在你身边了
If you're reading this, it means I'm no longer with you.
你现在起得靠自己了 你要坚强
You're on your own now, and you have to be strong.
无论你做什么 我都是你的父亲
No matter what you do, I am your father,
你是我的小心肝
and you're my little girl.
我会永远爱你
And I will always love you.
看看这边
Check it out.
一直向前
Straight ahead.
我觉得我们找到营地了
I think we found our camp.
看来没人啊
Looks empty.
没有看守 什么都没有
No guards, nothing.
废墟
Ghost town.
里根
Regan?
我听不到动静
I don't hear a thing.
我们从下面过去吧
Let's move in from below.
安全
Clear.
空无一人  外面的尸体一定是工人
Empty. The bodies outside must be the workers.
- 大屠杀  - 安全
- A massacre. - Clear.
没有枪伤
No bullet wounds.
没有枪战的痕迹  只有
No signs of firefight. Just...
被分尸的尸体
Ripped apart.
到底是谁这么心狠手辣
What the hell could have done this?
弗林
Flynn?
你发现了什么
What did you find?
脚印
Footprints.
看起来是不久前的
They look fresh.
闭嘴 这是我的问题
Shut up, it's my problem.
嘿 嗯 我们搜索了整个营地
Hey... yeah, we searched the entire camp.
无人生还
There's no one left here alive.
也没发现什么
Nothing more to see.
不 还不能走
No, we're not leaving.
我们现在返程 还能在天黑前回去
We go now, we might make it back before dark.
哦 他们要睡觉了吗
Oh, is it past their bedtime?
是的 是的
Yeah... yeah.
因为我们已经完成了任务 把你们带到营地
'Cause we did our job... got you to the camp.
这是我答应杰克逊的
That's what I told Jackson we'd do,
已经完成了
and it's done.
这是你的林地吗
Is this your jungle?
是的
Yes.
那就拿出你该有的样子
Then act like it.
你们不是为缉毒行动来的
You're not here for a drug bust.
布里格斯 我们一起守夜吧
Briggs... let's set up a watch.
轮流守 一直到明天早上
We'll take shifts till morning.
马托 你和你的部下
Mato... you and your men
可以清理下外面的尸体
can clean up the bodies outside.
我们去搜查制毒室
We'll search the lab.
他们在生产海洛因
They were producing heroin.
看看这
Look at this.
看这个
Check this out.
这具尸体和外面的不同
That body wasn't killed like the ones outside.
伤口和麦卡锡仓库里的
It's the same wounds as the junkie
瘾君子一样
in McCarthy's warehouse.
我捣毁过很多制毒窝点
I've raided dozens of drug labs,
从没见过这样的
I've never seen anything like this.
此事另有隐情
Something else was going on.
还是暖的
It's still warm.
他们在破坏证据
They were destroying evidence.
和人
And people.
计划周全 毫无破绽
No loose ends.
他们好像一直先我们一步
Like they were one step ahead of us.
斯拉维奇跟我说 我们有内鬼
Slavich told me they had someone on the inside.
内鬼  不可能吧
A mole? That's crazy.
那是什么
What is that?
嗯 是外皮
Yeah, it's skin.
嗯
Yeah.
某种身体组织 不是人类的
It's some kind of tissue, not human.
他们到底在这儿干嘛
What the hell were they doing here?
去掉痛苦
Taking the pain away.
芝加哥 伊利诺斯州 2012
还想拿奖赏么
You want a medal?
我交班时间快到了  滚边儿
My break's almost over. Shoo.
疯婊子
Crazy fucking bitch.
我会打电话给你的
I'll call you!
才怪
Not.
嘿
Hey.
在干什么
What are you doin'?
关你屁事 臭傻逼
None of your business, dick wad.
你说啥
What did you say?
你听到的  蠢驴
You heard me, donut ass.
面对墙站好
Up against the wall.
放了他
Let him go!
放了他 不然我开枪了
Let him go, or I'll shoot!
听见什么没  在外面吗
Hear anything? Is it out there?
我不知道  可能吧
I don't know. Could be.
天没亮 什么也干不了
Can't do much till morning.
至少第一个被五马分尸的会是布里格斯
At least Briggs will be the first one getting ripped apart.
什么
What?
他没让你这个猎人好过吧 处处针对你
After all the shit he gives you for being a Hunter?
布里格斯恨我是有原因的
Briggs has his reasons for hating me.
爱亦是
And loving me.
很复杂
It's complicated.
你们俩
Did you two...?
不不不 天
No. No. God, no.
我不是他的菜
I'm not his type.
而且 他喜欢独来独往
Besides, he's kind of a loner,
我怕你还没看出来
in case you hadn't figured that out yet.
也不能说我怪他
Can't say I blame him.
我见过一些人做出极恶之事
I've seen human beings do some heinous shit.
但我从没见过这样的
But I've never seen anything like that.
来点吧
This helps.
所以酒对你的影响不像
So alcohol doesn't affect you like...
不不  但我喜欢喝酒这种活动
No. No. But I like the ritual.
让我觉得自己是正常人
It makes me feel normal.
我和你相反
It's pretty much the opposite for me.
我喜欢它让我觉得自己没那么正常
I like how it makes me feel not normal.
你是不是一直看起来都那么像
Did you always look... so...
什么  人类
What? Human?
自打我记事起就是
As far as I can remember.
我一直以为自己是呢 直到我父母告诉我不是
Thought I was, until my parents told me I wasn't.
你的妻子 你从没怀疑过
Your wife... you never suspected?
什么
What?
她可能是外星人吗
That she could be from outer space?
不
No.
我特么为什么要那么想
Had no damn reason to think she might be.
但 看着你
But, watching you...
我觉得还真有可能
I'd say it's possible.
米格尔
Miguel!
米格尔 欧内斯托
Miguel, Ernesto!
回来  回来
Come back! Come back!
好运  我逃命去了
Good luck. I'll back off.
米格尔  你在哪里
Miguel! Where are you?
你死定了 你个混蛋
You're gonna fry, you bastard.
马托的手下全被杀死了
This killed all of Mato's men.
那是什么鬼
What the hell is that?
它要逃走了
It's getting away.
那是什么
What was that?
不管是什么
Whatever it was...
反正不是人类
it wasn't human.
我的手机呢  我要叫后援
Where's my cell phone? I'm calling in backup.
如果必要 我真要叫上所有军队
The whole God damn army if I have to.
我们要找到那东西 然后杀了它
We will find that thing and go kill it...
能告诉我 这到底是怎么一回事吗
Wanna tell me what the hell that was about?
保密协议  杰克逊的命令
Containment protocol. Jackson's orders.
他看到太多了  他会说出去的
He saw too much. He was about to talk.
她说得没错  地外反恐行动组的规定
She's right. ETU rules.
我们不能让别人知道这些
We can't let any of this get out.
杀死他手下的东西还在外游荡
Whatever killed his men is still out there.
我们必须通知杰克逊 走吧
We need to notify Jackson, get moving.
里根 如果我没有加入行动组
Regan, if I hadn't have joined the unit,
你也会把我处置掉吗
would you have... contained me?
不是人类外表吗
Not in human form?
那是披着什么皮的怪物
Well, what form is it in?
我也不太清楚
I don't know, exactly.
我只能确定是一个猎人
All I know for sure is that it's a Hunter.
马托也看见了吗
And Mato saw it?
他有没有被
Has he been...?
已经解决了
It's been handled.
你的所谓保密协议 令我们人手紧缺
Your protocol left us shorthanded.
我们需要额外支援  派空中之眼无人机过来
We need additional support. Eyes in the sky.
我尽力而为
I'll see what I can do.
我们现在就需要  等不到明天早上了
We need it now. Can't wait till the morning.
- 明白  - 那东西晚上也能行动
- Understood. - That thing can hunt at night.
它有优势
It has the advantage.
你能定位目标对象的位置吗
You have a location on the target?
它受伤了 而且很害怕
It's injured, scared.
我觉得它会躲到山里去
I think it'll head to the mountains.
你觉得还是你确定
You think or you know?
反正我会这么做
That's what I would do.
就我们对他们语言的了解而言 还算说得过去
That makes sense with what we understand about their language.
地势越高
Higher elevation means more miles
越能先发制人
to anticipate potential attacks.
我们原本一个小时之内就可以派无人机过去
We could have a drone out there in an hour.
出什么状况了
And then what happens?
有个爱荷华州的22岁的
22-year-old kid from Iowa
斯诺登狂饭 用游戏机控制器
with an Xbox controller and a Snowden complex
把无人机黑掉了
gets one of these things in his sights?
怎么解决
How do we contain that?
车到山前必有路
We'll cross that bridge when we come to it.
我会联系兰利
I'll reach out to Langley.
如果我们真想抓到它 现在就应该出发了
If we wanna catch this thing, we gotta leave now.
ETU曾经抓到过跟你不一样的猎人吗
Has ETU ever caught one that doesn't look like you?
我们从未抓到过任何形态的活口
We've never captured one alive in any form.
那么我们这次最好能抓到一个 对吧
Then we better... catch this one, right?
天那么黑 我们怎么找得到它
How we gonna find it in the dark?
有志者事竟成
You can find anything if you want it badly enough.
库克郡惩教中心 伊利诺斯州 芝加哥市 2012年
艾莉森 你好
Hello, Allison.
我叫特拉斯·杰克逊
My name is Truss Jackson.
我来自国土安全部
Homeland Security.
我不是来伤害你的
I'm not here to hurt you.
看什么看 你个糟老头
Stop staring, you dirty old freak.
怎么着 以前没见过女的
What, you never seen a girl before?
只是没见过你这样的
Not like you.
几年前  我把你的
I have an... old photograph of you
一张老照片录入系统
that I put into the system years ago,
就怕你万一哪天被警察逮捕
just in case you ever got arrested.
就是这张
And here you are.
挺可爱
Cute kid.
但不是我
But that's not me.
艾莉森·里根 来自西佛吉尼亚州的塞克莱顿市
Allison Regan of Circleton, West Virginia.
泰德·里根与利安娜·里根的女儿
Daughter of Ted and Liana Regan.
没听说过
Never heard of 'em.
16岁时 家里被不明入侵者闯入 而失踪
Disappeared age 16 after a home invasion by unidentified intruders.
你确定这不是你吗
You sure that's not who you are?
行动
Go.
兰利不允许
Langley said no.
- 行动终止  - 为什么
- You have to abort. - Why?
见鬼
Bullshit!
如果没有后援 你们不堪一击
Without backup, you're vulnerable.
没有无人机 你们什么都看不见
Without a drone, you're blind.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
它受伤了  优势在我们这边
It's injured. We have the advantage.
它可是猎人的新变体
It's a new form of Hunter.
行动终止
Abort.
这是命令
That's an order.
信号不好  你要我们汇报吗
You're breaking up. You said report?
行动终止  我说终止
Abort! I said abort.
收到  我们会在完成任务后向您汇报 完毕
Copy that! We'll complete the mission and report, over.
卡罗尔
Carroll!
我们这回要倒大霉了
We're gonna catch shit for that.
最好物有所值
Well, we better make it worth it.
在树上
In the trees!
布里格斯
Briggs!
真特么见鬼
You piece of shit!
- 我没事  - 是那些毒贩子设下的陷阱
- I'm okay. - A perimeter trap from the drug cartel.
用得着你说
Oh, now you tell me.
准备好了吗  数到三
Ready? On three.
- 来吧  - 1
- Go on. - One...
喀嗒声越来越弱了
The clicks are getting fainter.
好吧 你去追吧
All right, you go.
我来照看布里格斯
I'll take care of Briggs.
她会被那个生物撕碎的
She could get ripped by whatever that thing is.
也可能反过来
Or she tears it up.
正好两不耽误 双赢
What they call a win-win.
是啊
Right.
里根又怎么惹着你了
So what's your beef with Regan?
我可不像你那么喜欢人形猎人
Oh, I don't like human Hunters like you do.
她真他妈能干
She's been pretty damn useful.
她不是我见过的唯一一个猎人
She's not the only one I've met.
我曾经与澳洲特种部队在阿富汗执行任务
I was with Australian Special Forces in Afghanistan.
我们还以为找到了恐怖分子的巢穴
We thought we were hitting a terrorist cell.
结果房间里只有一个人
Turned out to be just one guy in a room.
我们两人冲进去
Two of us went in.
火力大开
Opened fire, both clips.
那人毫发未伤
Nothing.
然后
And then...
它扑向布兰登
it leapt at Brendan
把他撕成了碎片
and it ripped him apart.
不慌不忙 戏弄意味十足
But slowly... playfully.
就像猫戏弄老鼠一样
Like a cat.
整个过程中
And the whole time,
它一直盯着我
it kept looking at me.
就像那是一场表演
Like it was a show.
猎人夺走了你所爱之人
Hunters took the one you love.
我也有同样遭遇
They did that to me, too.
你不能相信她
You can't trust her.
不管外表再怎么纯良
And whatever they look like on the surface...
它们骨子里还是恶魔
they're monsters underneath.
伊利诺斯州 芝加哥市 2012年
你太狠了吧
You're ruthless.
世界尽在我的掌控之中
World domination cometh.
你的杀人本能是来自父母的吗
You get the killer instinct from your parents?
我父母不是早死了么
My parents are dead, aren't they?
其实 我们对你 你的父母
Truth is, we don't know much about anything about...
都了解甚少
your parents, about you, about any of it.
所以你狗屁不懂
So you don't know shit.
你不了解我
Not about me.
没人了解我
No one does.
这么多年来 你一直留着父亲给你的信
You kept his letter from your dad for years.
每个人都需要精神支柱
Everybody needs someone.
你的父母
Your parents...
他们和你一样
they were like you.
对吗
Weren't they?
是
Yeah.
我们一样
They were like me.
那你是什么
And what are you?
我不知道
I don't know.